WestConn Serials and Publications Catalogs, Yearbooks, View Books, Registration Booklets and Academic Journals RG 8.1
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Yearbooks, 53888
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1989; 53905 (Item 56)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1990; 53904 (Item 57)
    10 copies
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1991; 53903 (Item 58)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1992; 53902 (Item 59)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1993; 53901 (Item 60)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 1994; 53900 (Item 61)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 1995; 53899 (Item 62)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 1996; 53898 (Item 63)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 1997; 53897 (Item 64)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 1998; 53896 (Item 65)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 1999; 53895 (Item 66)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2000; 53894 (Item 67)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 2001; 53893 (Item 68)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2002; 53892 (Item 69)
  - Western Connecticut State University Colonial, 2006; 53891 (Item 70)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2008; 53890 (Item 71)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2009; 53889 (Item 72)
- Miscellaneous short runs, 54512
  Biographical / Historical
  Danbury Teacher's Quarterly (1941) The students of Danbury State Teacher's College produced this literary journal. Only one issue exists in the Archives.
  The WasteCann-(1987) It was an "underground" publication that served as a backlash against university president Stephen Feldman and his administrative staff. Hostile words along with the characterization of President Feldman as Adolf Hitler expressed the feelings of this publication. The author, or authors, of this publication is still unknown.
  - Academic Ties 1993-1994, 54525 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Focus 2001-2002, 54524 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Footnotes Fall 1999, 54523 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Western Pillars/The Pillars 1999-2003, 54522 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
  - West Star Aug.1999, 54521 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wescon Summer News, vol. 1, no. 3 Jul 17,1967, 54520 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Western News, vol. 1, no. 1 Jan.1989, 54519 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - The Western Way, vol. 1 1988-1989, 54518 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - The Western Way, vol. 2 1989-1990, 54517 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The Western Way, vol. 3 1990-1991, 54516 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - The Western Way, vol. 4 1991-1992, 54515 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Hall Magazine, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Scenes, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - WestConntributors, 2005-2009 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    9 issues
  - Journal of Undergraduate Psychology Research, 2006-2010 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    3 issues
  - Danbury Teacher's Quarterly 1941; vol. 1, no. 1, 54514 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The WasteCann, 1987; vol. I, no. I-IV; VI-VII; vol. II, no. I and other underground publications, 54513 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- CLIO, 54459
  Clio- (1973-present) This publication is published by the students of the History Department. It began as a quarterly journal, but in 1986 became an annual publication.
  - CLIO, Nov 1973, 54510 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CLIO, Feb 1974, 54509 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CLIO, May 1974, 54508 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CLIO, [Feb 1975], 1974; 54507 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The folder originally listed September 1974. It is unclear wether the September issue is missing or the folder was initially mislabeled.
  - CLIO, Apr 1975, 54506 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - CLIO, May 1975, 54505 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CLIO, Dec 1975, 54504 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - CLIO, Mar 1976, 54503 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - CLIO, May 1976, 54502 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CLIO, Fall 1976, 54501 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CLIO, Winter 1976-77, 1976-1977; 54500 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - CLIO, Spring 1977, 54499 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - CLIO, Spring 1977, 54498 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - CLIO, Fall 1977, 54497 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - CLIO, Spring 1978, 54496 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CLIO, Fall 1978, 54495 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CLIO, Spring 1979, 54494 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CLIO, Fall 1979, 54493 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CLIO, Spring 1980, 54492 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CLIO, Fall 1980, 54491 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CLIO, Spring 1981, 54490 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CLIO, Winter 1981-82, 1981-1982; 54489 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CLIO, Fall 1982, 54488 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - CLIO, Spring 1983, 54487 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CLIO, Fall 1983, 54486 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CLIO, Winter 1983-84, 1983-1984; 54485 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - CLIO, Winter 1984-85, 1984-1985; 54484 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - CLIO, Winter 1985, 54483 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - CLIO, Spring 1986, 54482 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - CLIO, Spring 1987, 54481 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - CLIO, Spring 1988, 54480 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - CLIO, Spring 1989, 54479 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CLIO, Spring 1990, 54478 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CLIO, Spring 1991, 54477 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - CLIO, Spring 1992, 54476 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - CLIO, Spring 1993, 54475 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - CLIO, Spring 1994, 54474 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
  - CLIO, Spring 1995, 54473 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - CLIO, Spring 1996, 54472 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - CLIO, Spring 1997, 54471 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CLIO, Spring 1998, 54470 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - CLIO, Spring 1999, 54469 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - CLIO, Spring 2000, 54468 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - CLIO, Spring 2001, 54467 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - CLIO, Spring 2002, 54466 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CLIO, Spring 2005, 54465 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CLIO, Spring 2006, 54464 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CLIO, Spring 2007, 54463 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - CLIO, Spring 2008, 54462 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - CLIO, Spring 2009, 54461 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - CLIO, Winter 2009-2010, 54460 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Conatus [continued by Black and White], 54402
  Conatus-(1960-present) This is the literary journal for the university. It was originally published bi-annually, but in 1971 it became an annual publication. The publication includes poetry, essays, short stories, and artwork.
  - Conatus, Fall 1960; vol. VII, no. 1, 54457 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Conatus, Spring 1961; vol. VII, no. 2, 54456 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Conatus, Winter 1961; vol. VIII, no. 1, 54455 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Conatus, Spring 1962; vol. VIII, no. 2, 54454 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Conatus, Fall 1962; vol. IX, no. 1, 54453 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Conatus, Spring 1963; vol. IX, no. 2, 54452 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Conatus, Fall 1963; vol. X, no. 1, 54451 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Conatus, Spring 1964; vol. X, no. 2, 54450 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Conatus, Fall 1964; vol. XI, no. 1, 54449 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Conatus, Spring 1965; vol. XII, no. 2, 54448 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Conatus, Winter 1965-66, vol. XII, no. 3, 1965-1966; 54447 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Conatus, Spring 1966; vol. XIII, no. 1, 54446 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Conatus, Fall 1966; vol. XIII, no. 2, 54445 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Conatus, Spring 1967; vol. XIV, no. 1, 54444 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Conatus, Fall 1967; vol. XV, 54443 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Conatus, Spring 1968, vol. XVI, 54442 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Conatus, Fall 1968, 54441 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Conatus, Dec 1969; vol. 19, no. 1, 54440 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Conatus, December 1969, Portfolio 1; vol. 1, no. 1, 54439 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Conatus, 1970; vol. 20, no. 1, 54438 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Conatus, May 1971; vol. 21, no. 1, 54437 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Conatus, May 1972; vol. 22, no. 1, 54436 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Conatus, 1973, 54435 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Conatus, 1974, 54434 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Conatus, 1976, 54433 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Conatus, 1977, 54432 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Conatus, 1978, 54431 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Conatus, 1979-1980, 54430 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Conatus, 1981, 54429 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Conatus, 1982, 54428 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Conatus, 1983, 54427 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Conatus, 1984, 54426 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Conatus, 1985, 54425 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Conatus, 1986, 54424 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Conatus, 1987, 54423 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Conatus, 1988, 54422 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Conatus, 1989, 54421 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Conatus, 1990, 54420 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Conatus, 1991, 54419 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Conatus, 1992, 54418 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Conatus, 1993, 54417 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Conatus, 1995, 54416 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - Conatus, 1996, 54415 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
  - Conatus, 1997, 54414 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Conatus, 1998, 54413 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Conatus, 1999, 54412 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Conatus, 2000, 54411 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Conatus, 2001, 54410 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Conatus, 2002, 54409 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Conatus, 2003, 54408 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Conatus, 2004, 54407 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Conatus, 2005, 54406 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - black & white, journal for the arts, Spring 2008, no. 1, 54405 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Black & White Journal, Spring 2009, no. 2, 54404 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Black & White Journal for the arts, Spring 2010, no. 3, 54403 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Courier, 54387
  The Courier-(1954-1960) This was the literary journal produced by the students between 1954-1960. It began as an extension of the student newspaper The Supplement. Starting in 1960, the journal was renamed Conatus.
  - Courier, December 1954, vol. 1, no.1, 54400 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Courier, April 1955; vol. 1, no. 2, 54399 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Courier, June 1955; vol. 1, no. 3, 54398 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Courier, Fall 1955; vol. 2, no. 1, 54397 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Courier, Winter 1956; vol. 2, no. 2, 54396 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Courier, Spring 1956; vol. 2, no. 3, 54395 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Courier, Fall 1956; vol. 3, no 1, 54394 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Courier, Fall 1957; vol. 4, no. 1, 54393 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Courier, Spring 1958; vol. 4, no. 2, 54392 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Courier, Fall 1958; vol. 5, no. 1, 54391 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Courier, Spring 1959; vol. 5, no. 2, 54390 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Courier, Fall 1959; vol. 6, no. 1, 54389 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Courier, Spring 1960; vol. 6, no. 2, 54388 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Conjunction, 54379
  Conjunction-(1994-1997) This bi-annual publication was produced by students of the English Department.
  - Conjunction, Spring 1994, no. 2, 54385 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Conjunction, Fall 1994, no.1, 54384 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Conjunction, Winter 1994, 54383 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Conjunction, Spring 1995, no.1, 54382 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Conjunction, Spring 1996, no. 3, 54381 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Conjunction, Fall 1996, no. 2, 54380 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Prisma, 54368
  Prisma-(1986-present). The students of the Art Department began this annual publication to exhibit their work with detailed photographs. This collection is incomplete and has several gaps.
  - Prisma, 1986-2008; 54377 (Box 19, Folder 1-12)
    Arts magazine published by the Art Department at WCSU.
- Smoke Signals, 54349
  Smoke Signals-(1957-1973) This was the official student handbook of the college. Published annually by the Cooperative Government Association (later the Student Government Association). The title reflects the fact the athletic teams were known as the Indians. It stopped publication in the mid 1970s when the school changed the name to the Colonials.
  Memorial Hall Magazine, (c.a. 1964) This magazine was published to illustrate the different kinds of events and activities that took place in Memorial Hall. We have only one issue.
  The Pennington (1935). One issue which contains names of faculty, class officers, seniors, clubs and officers, Student Council Officers (1932-1935), and "News from Class Members" (alumni).
  - Smoke Signals, 1957-58 (DSTC), 1957-1958; 54366 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Smoke Signals, 1958-59 (DSTC), 1958-1959; 54365 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Smoke Signals, 1959-60 (DSTC), 1959-1960; 54364 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Smoke Signals, 1961-62 (DSTC), 1961-1962; 54363 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Smoke Signals, 1962-63 (DSTC), 1962-1963; 54362 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Smoke Signals, 1963-64 (DSTC), 1963-1964; 54361 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Smoke Signals, 1964-65 (DSC), 1964-1965; 54360 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Smoke Signals, 1965-66 (DSC), 1965-1966; 54359 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Smoke Signals, 1966-67 (DSC), 1966-1967; 54358 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Smoke Signals, 1967-68 (WCSC), 1967-1968; 54357 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Smoke Signals, 1968-69 (WCSC), 1968-1969; 54356 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Smoke Signals, 1969-70 (WCSC), 1969-1970; 54355 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Smoke Signals, 1970-71 (WCSC), 1970-1971; 54354 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Smoke Signals, 1972 (WCSC), 54353 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Smoke Signals, 1973 (WCSC), 54352 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Hall Magazine, 1964; 54351 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - The Pennington, 1935; 54350 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Social Science Journal, 54332
  Social Science Journal-(1995-present) As the title suggests, this annual publication is published by the students of the Social Science Department.
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 1995, 54347 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 1996, 54346 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 1997, 54345 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 1998, 54344 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 1999, 54343 (Box 21, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 2000, 54342 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 2001, 54341 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 2002, 54340 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Journal, Fall 2003, 54339 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Social Science Journal, 2004, 54338 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Social Science Journal, 2005, 54337 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Social Science Journal, Spring 2006, 54336 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Social Science Journal, 2008, 54335 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Social Science Journal, 2009, 54334 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Social Science Journal, 2010, 54333 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Social Sciences Journal, 2012 (Item 22, Folder 5)
- Economic Journal (Western Economic Journal), 54324
  Western Economic Journal-(1985-1993) This annual publication was published by the students of the Economic Club.
  - Economic Journal, Fall 1985, 54330 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Economic Journal, Fall 1986, 54329 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Economic Journal, Spring 1988, 54328 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Economic Journal, Spring 1991, 54327 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Economic Journal, Spring 1992, 54326 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Economic Journal, Spring 1993, 54325 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Western Scholar, 54313
  Western Scholar-(1998-2007) This annual publication, produced by students, serves as the forum where ideas and opinions can be heard.
  - Western Scholar, 1998, 54322 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Western Scholar, 1999, 54321 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Western Scholar, 2000, 54320 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Western Scholar, 2001, 54319 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Western Scholar, 2003, 54318 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Western Scholar, 2004, 54317 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Western Scholar, 2005, 54316 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Western Scholar, 2006, 54315 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Western Scholar, 2007, 54314 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Western Report, 54295
  - Western Report vol. 1, no. 1-28, 1993-1994, 54311 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Western Report vol. 2, no. 1-31, 1994-1995, 54310 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Western Report vol. 3, no. 1-33, 1995-1996, 54309 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Western Report vol. 4, no. 1-33, 1996-1997, 54308 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Western Report vol. 5, no. 1-28, 1997-1998, 54307 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Western Report vol. 6, no. 1-28, 1998-1999, 54306 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Western Report vol. 7, no. 1-31, 1999-2000, 54305 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Western Report vol. 8, no. 1-32, 2000-2001, 54304 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - WestConn Report vol. 9, no. 1-30, 2001-2002, 54303 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - WestConn Report vol. 10, no. 1-32, 2002-2003, 54302 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
  - WestConn Report vol. 11, no. 1-29, 2003-2004, 54301 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
  - WestConn Report vol. 12, no. 1-23, 2004-2005, 54300 (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
  - WestConn Report vol. 13, no. 1-29, 2005-2006, 54299 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
  - Westconn Report vol. 14, no. 1-16, 2006-2007, 54298 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - WestConn Report vol. 15, no. 1-17, 2007-2008, 54297 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - WestConn Report vol. 16, no. 1-9, 2008-2009, 54296 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Telephone Directories, 54277
  - Faculty/Staff, 1971-1976; 54293 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Students (full time, graduate and undergraduate) 1979, 54292 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Faculty/Staff 1984-1998, 54291 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Faculty/Staff 1994-1995, 54290 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Student/Faculty/Staff 2000-2001, 54289 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Student/Faculty/Staff 2002-2003, 54288 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Student/Faculty/Staff 2003-2004, 54287 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Student/Faculty/Staff 2004-2005, 54286 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Student/Faculty/Staff 2005-2006, 54285 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Faculty/Staff 2006-2007, 54284 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Faculty/Staff 2008-2009, 54283 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Directory, 1989, 54282 (Box shelf, Folder 73)
  - Alumni Directory, 1994, 54281 (Box shelf, Folder 74)
  - Alumni Directory, 1999, 54280 (Box shelf, Folder 75)
  - Alumni Directory, 2003, 54279 (Box shelf, Folder 76)
  - Alumni Directory, 2008, 54278 (Box shelf, Folder 77)
- Communique, 54273
  - Communique, vol. 1 - vol. 6, 1998-2004, 54275 (Box 28)
  - Communique, vol. 7 - vol. 10, 2004-2009, 54274 (Box 29)
- Cupola, 54263
  - The Cupola (supercedes Alumni News), Fall 2010, 54271 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - The Cupola, Spring 2011, 54270 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Cupola, 2012 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- The Gates, 54526
  - the Gates, Inaugural Issue, April/May 2009, 54268 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - the Gates, August/September 2009, 54267 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - the Gates, October/November 2009, 54266 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - the Gates, February/March 2010, 54265 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - the Gates, Fall 2010, 54264 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- WestConn Matters (Western Matters), 54253
  - Western Matters (published by WCSU and The News-Times), 0; 54261 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Western Matters, Fall 1998, 54260 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Western Matters, Fall 1999, 54259 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Western Matters, Fall 2000, 54258 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - WestConn Matters, Fall 2001, 54257 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - WestConn Matters, Fall 2002, 54256 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - WestConn Matters, Fall 2003, 54255 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - WestConn Matters, Fall 2004, 54254 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- WestConn Guides, 54247
  - News-Times, undated; 54251 (Box shelf, Folder 78)
  - WCSU Student Welcome Guide, Jan 2009, 54250 (Box shelf, Folder 79)
  - WCSU Student Welcome Guide, Aug 2009, 54249 (Box shelf, Folder 80)
  - WCSU Student Welcome Guide, Jan 2010, 54248 (Box shelf, Folder 81)
- Convocation, Commencement, and Other Programs
  - Academic Convocation, 1983; 38178 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1906-1910; 38177 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1911-1913, 1915; 38176 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1917-1920; 38175 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1921-1927; 38174 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1928-1930; 38173 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1931-1936; 38172 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1938-1942; 38171 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1943-1945; 38170 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1947-1950; 38169 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1951-1952; 38168 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1953-1956; 38167 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1957-1959; 38166 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1960-1963; 38165 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1964-1967; 38164 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1968-1969; 38163 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1970-1971; 38162 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1972-1973; 38161 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Programs, 1974; 38160 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (Midyear Commencement Programs), 1972-1975; 38159 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1975-1977; 38158 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (Midyear Commencement Programs), 1977-1978; 38157 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1978-1980; 38156 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1981; 38155 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1982; 38154 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1983; 38153 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1984; 38152 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1985; 38151 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1986; 38150 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (includes Recognition Program), 1987; 38149 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1988; 38148 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (includes Recognition Program), 1989; 38147 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1990; 38146 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1991; 38145 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1992; 38144 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (includes Recognition Program), 1992-1994; 38143 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1993; 38142 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1994; 38141 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (Includes Commencement Address), 1995; 38140 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1996; 38139 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (includes Recognition Program), 1996-1997; 38138 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1997; 38137 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1998; 38136 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (includes Recognition Program), 1998-1999; 38135 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 1999; 38134 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 2000; 38133 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (includes Recognition Program), 2000-2001; 38132 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 2001; 38131 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 2002; 38130 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 2003; 38129 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Commencement Programs, 2004; 38128 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations, 2005; 38127 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Commencement Programs, 2006; 38126 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Commencement Programs and Invitations (1st graduate commencement), 2007; 38125 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Programs, 2008; 38124 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Commencement Programs, 2009; 38123 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Commencement Programs, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Commencement Programs, 2015 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Commencement Program, 2016 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Commencement Program, 2018 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1966-1974; 38115 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1976, 1978-1979; 38114 (Box 34, Folder 2)